feedity.com 2018-08-12

# Feedity Privacy Policy - RSS Feed Data and Security Policy

At Feedity, we respect your privacy & information security, just as we value our own.

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from Feedity (the "Service").

**Information We Collect**

When you visit the Service, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Service, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Service, and information about how you interact with the Service. We refer to this automatically-collected information as "Device Information."

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

\- "Cookies" are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website, and stored on your device. We use session cookies to operate the Service, and preference cookies to remember your preferences and various settings. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

\- "Log files" track actions occurring on the Service, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

\- "Web beacons," "tags," and "pixels" are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Service.

Additionally when you signup or make a purchase, or attempt to signup or make a purchase through the Service, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, payment information (including credit card numbers, PayPal account Id), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as "Order Information."

We do not store your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors, listed below, whose use of your personal information is governed by their privacy policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

When we talk about "Personal Information" in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

**How We Use Your Personal Information?**

We use the collected Personal Information for various purposes:

\- To provide and maintain the Service and related services  
\- To notify you about changes to the Service  
\- To allow you to participate in interactive features of the Service when you choose to do so  
\- To provide customer support  
\- To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service  
\- To monitor the usage of the Service  
\- To detect, prevent and address technical issues  
\- To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information.

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Service (including processing your payment information, arranging for digital delivery, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

\- Communicate with you;  
\- Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and  
\- When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Service (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Service, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

**Sharing Your Personal Information**

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.

\- We use Stripe to process secure online credit-card payments -- you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: <https://stripe.com/privacy>.  
\- We also use PayPal to process secure online payments -- you can read more about how PayPal uses your Personal Information here: <https://www.paypal.com/privacy>.  
\- We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Service -- you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.  
\- We use Campaign Monitor to send email marketing campaigns, email newsletters and other informational emails to Service users and customers -- you can read more about how Campaign Monitor uses your Personal Information here: <https://www.campaignmonitor.com/policies/#privacy-policy>.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

**Behavioural Advertising**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with marketing communications or targeted advertisements we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative's ("NAI") educational page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work>.

You can opt out of targeted advertising on:

\- Google, at <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous>  
\- Facebook, at <https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads>  
\- Twitter, at <https://twitter.com/settings/safety>  
\- LinkedIn, at <https://www.linkedin.com/psettings/>  
\- Bing, at <https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads>

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance's opt-out portal at: [http://optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/).

**Do Not Track**

Please note that we do not alter our Service's data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

**Your Rights**

You can use some of the features of the Service without registering, thereby limiting the type of information that we collect.

You may unsubscribe from receiving certain informational or promotional emails from us. If you wish to do so, simply follow the instructions found at the end of the email. Even if you unsubscribe, we may still contact you for informational, transactional, account-related, or similar purposes.

You can disable the use of cookies. Many browsers have an option for disabling cookies, which may prevent your browser from accepting new cookies or enable selective use of cookies. Please note that, if you choose not to accept cookies, some features and the personalization of the Service may no longer work for you.

You can also disable the use of script code (JavaScript). Many browsers have an option for disabling script code (JavaScript), which may prevent your browser from utilizing client-side code for interactive behavior on webpages. Please note that, if you choose to disable script code (JavaScript), most features of the Service will no longer work for you.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), your data protection rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) allow you to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Service), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Australia and the United States.

**Data Retention**

We will retain and use your Personal Information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax, or accounting requirements).

We will also retain and use your Personal Information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

When you signup or make a purchase through the Service, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

**Children's Privacy**

The Service is not intended for children under the age of 13.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, then please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

**Contact Us**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at [info@feedity.com](mailto:info@feedity.com) or through our online contact form.
